seocruse.co.uk 2014-08-19

# SEO Cruse - Fantastic SEO All In One Place!

Please refer to our Privacy Policy for important information on the use of cookies. By continuing to use this website, you agree to this.

### Privacy Policy.

This section was last updated on 05/06/2014.

##### Information Collection & Use

SEO Cruse is the sole owner of the information collected on this web site. We will not sell or share this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. SEO Cruse collects information from our users at several different points on our website. We request information from the user on our enquiry forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name, email and telephone numbers etc). This information is used to fulfil customer's enquiries and/or orders. We might get back to the customer to provide the information requested by the customer (such as a quote). A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our web site. Security of Your Information We store your personally identifiable information and payment information in a secure and encrypted database.

##### Online Website Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounting staff or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

##### Outgoing External Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. SEO Cruse is not responsisble for the information, content or opinions contained on external websites, including those of our clients.

##### Choice/Opt-out

If you use this site to purchase services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications on our order form. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our companies may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us directly. Users of our site are notified when their information is being collected or used by any third parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require a third party, or not.

##### Children's Privacy

Our service is not available to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under the age of 13. 

##### General

When you sign up for a service provided by us, we may ask you to provide us with contact information such as your name, address, telephone numbers and payment information such as expiry date and card number. If you need to contact us for customer support , we may ask for proof of who you are to confirm you are the owner of the services you are enquiring about. When you vist our website we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of vist and the pages you have viewed. We will also place a cookie that will identify you as a repeat vistitor or customer when you vist our Web site. See "What is a cookie" below. [If we send you an e-mail, we may include a marker that will allow us to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed.]  
A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our web site. Security of Your Information We store your personally identifiable information and payment information in a secure and encrypted database.

#### Need Better Rankings? Get To Page One Now!

SEO Cruse can now provide our clients anything from 5 - 50 Keywords each month.   
We now also offer amazing discounts email us now for details!
